If you're trying to make hard ice cream
in the Ninja Creamy and just can't seem
to get the texture right, you're
probably just using the mix-in setting
too late. Let me explain. I think the
majority of you would say this is too
crumbly to add mixins at this point. But
if you want hard ice cream, this is when
you have to do it. The ideal texture
before adding mix-ins should be slightly
crumbly. When you go to scrape down the
sides of your pint, as you should be
doing, the ice cream should be slightly
melted and hold together just [music]
barely. Here's an example. This was a
cookies and cream pint. You can see
while I scraped down the sides, it is
like slightly melted and it's just
barely holding together. Honestly, it
looks very crumbly. But then you run the
mixing setting and it comes out as
perfect Ben & Jerry style hard ice
cream. Now, obviously, if you want like
a soft serve consistency or a blizzard
consistency, this is not the method you
should be using. For those, you're fine
with using the mixing setting or respin
setting before adding your mixins. And
if you want it super soft, you can add
milk between spins to loosen it up even
further. And what I mean by that is that
they usually come out looking like
these. And a lot of people like this
texture, but I know that there are some
people out there that want hard ice
cream and just can't seem to get it. And
this is probably